{
  "Questionnaire": [
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "1. HAVE YOU OR SOMEONE IN YOUR HOUSEHOLD TESTED POSITIVE FOR COVID-19?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "2. DO YOU HAVE ANY OF THE FOLLOWING NEW OR WORSENING SYMPTOMS OR SIGNS LIKE FEVER OR CHILLS?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "DIFFICULTY BREATHING OR SHORTNESS OF BREATH?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "MUSCLE OR BODY ACHES?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "LOSS OF TASTE OR SMELL?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "SORE THROAT?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 0, 
      "question": "CONGESTION OR RUNNY NOSE?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "3. HAVE YOU TRAVELLED OUTSIDE OF CANADA IN THE PAST 14 DAYS?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "4. HAVE YOU BEEN IN DIRECT CONTACT WITH SOMEONE WHO HAS TESTED POSITIVE FOR COVID-19 IN THE PAST 24 DAYS?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }, 
    {
      "correctIndex": 1, 
      "question": "5. HAVE YOU OR SOMEONE IN YOUR HOUSEHOLD BEEN DIRECTED BY A HEALTH CARE PROVIDER, INCLUDING A PUBLIC HEALTH PROFESSIONAL, TO ISOLATE?", 
      "answers": [
        "Yes", 
        "No"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
